<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Rob Wiltshire</title>
 <link href="http://www.robertwiltshire.co.uk/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://www.robertwiltshire.co.uk/"/>
 <updated>2018-02-24T17:37:50+00:00</updated>
 <id>http://www.robertwiltshire.co.uk</id>
 <author>
   <name>Rob Wiltshire</name>
   <email>info@robertwiltshire.co.uk</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>GitHubbin' it.</title>
   <link href="http://www.robertwiltshire.co.uk/2018/02/24/githubbin-it/"/>
   <updated>2018-02-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.robertwiltshire.co.uk/2018/02/24/githubbin-it</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Just a quick post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve ditched the conventional ways of hosting for this site for using github-pages instead. It makes sense, cos its free hosting. And I’ve no need to be using PHP all the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It helps switch my brain back to thinking about simple static websites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kind of like how we used to do it back in ‘99.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The everyday web still inspires me.</title>
   <link href="http://www.robertwiltshire.co.uk/2016/10/28/the-everyday-web/"/>
   <updated>2016-10-28T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.robertwiltshire.co.uk/2016/10/28/the-everyday-web</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It’s amazing how far the web has come in all that time from being so wild, so &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.washingtonpost.com/sf/business/2015/05/30/net-of-insecurity-part-1/&quot;&gt;insecure&lt;/a&gt;, so fresh and new, to the web we have today that is so banal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/88WFtJKH8k0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:0.8em;&quot;&gt;I always used to try to run over all of the ducks in my speedboat in Spy Hunter&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to imagine kids these days getting excited about a bit of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ajax_(programming)#History&quot;&gt;Ajax&lt;/a&gt;, to be honest I probably wouldn’t have been excited by Ajax when I was nine I was to absorbed with playing &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spy_Hunter&quot;&gt;Spy Hunter&lt;/a&gt; on my &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/ZX_Spectrum&quot;&gt;Spectrum&lt;/a&gt; when I was nine. I didn’t even know what a modem was, let alone know anything about &lt;em&gt;electronic communication&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/t_ggAhOeRc0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:0.8em;&quot;&gt;&quot;Ajax is that floor cleaning stuff that mum uses&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t care if anyone thinks its nerdy to love all this stuff. I love it. If I see a new bit of fancy UI, I’ll instantly F12 it just so I can poke around someone’s CSS or javascript. (Of course you could do more delving &lt;em&gt;back in the day&lt;/em&gt; before everyone started minifying everything).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know stuff like Ajax is such a commonplace, yet largely invisible thing on today’s web. But I still think Ajax is still a bit cool, a little bit like magic.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>blog || !blog</title>
   <link href="http://www.robertwiltshire.co.uk/2016/10/26/to-blog-or-to-not-blog/"/>
   <updated>2016-10-26T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.robertwiltshire.co.uk/2016/10/26/to-blog-or-to-not-blog</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;To be honest, I’m not much of a blogger. I’m lazy and I have little motivation. But I’m giving it a crack, and it might actually turn into something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been a web guy for the best part of twenty years, and before that I was just a kid that grew up with home computing and video games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its not the most interesting background story, I’ll admit.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
